http://www.joyelawfirm.com/privacy-policy/

Skip Content
HomeOur FirmContact Us menu
(888) 324-3100
In The News free consultation scholarship program Newsletter
Our AttorneysOur FounderPartnersMark JoyeKen HarrellNorth Charleston OfficeChristopher McCoolMatthew W. JacksonPatrick L. JenningsRyan LeBlancJeff GerardiMilton D. Stratos IIBrent H. ArantRandell Croft Stoney IIIWilliam AscheMyra WhitenerMyrtle Beach OfficeJohn RoxonPatrick SarsfieldColumbia OfficeSydney LynnEliza LynchClinton OfficeDavis RiceOf CounselMark BringardnerAbout UsOur ResultsTestimonialsJoye In The CommunityJoye Scholarship ProgramOur Practice AreasAccidentsPersonal InjuryWorkers’ CompensationCar AccidentsNursing Home AbuseDefective Medical DevicesDefective DrugsDefective ProductsMedical MalpracticePremises LiabilityNegligent SecurityVeterans’ DisabilityContact UsNorth CharlestonColumbiaMyrtle BeachClintonOur Communities
Home » Privacy Policy
tap to call directions
Privacy Policy
free consultation
To find out how we can help you, call us at 877-936-9707 or fill out our online contact form for a free and confidential claim evaluation. Our Policy for Protecting Your Online PrivacyThis website, joyelawfirm.com, uses the Google AdWords remarketing service to advertise on third-party websites (including Google) to previous visitors to our site.This could mean that we advertise to previous visitors who have not completed a task on our site such as using the contact form to submit an inquiry. Advertising could be in the form of an advertisement on the Google search results page or a site in the Google Display Network.Third-party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on someone’s past visits to the joyelawfirm.com website. Any data collected will be used in accordance with our own privacy policy and Google’s privacy policy.You can set preferences for how Google advertises to you by using the Google Ad Preferences page. You can also opt out of interest-based advertising entirely by adjusting cookie settings or permanently using a browser plug-in.Joyelawfirm.com uses Google Analytics to help analyze how visitors use the site. The tool uses “cookies.” These are text files placed on your computer to collect standard Internet log information and visitor behavior information in an anonymous form, including Internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, Internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp and number of clicks. This information is used to analyze trends, administer the site, track the user’s movement in the aggregate and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses, etc., are not linked to personally identifiable information. The information generated by the cookie about your use of the website (including IP address) is transmitted to Google. This information is then used to evaluate visitors’ use of the website and to compile statistical reports on website activity forjoyelawfirm.com.As part of our commitment to transparency and your privacy, we provide the following links to opt-out of cookies provided by both our first-party ad server and many third-party advertising partners who may be engaging in online behavioral advertising:First-Party Opt-out – Please visit this link to opt-out of cookies from our first-party ad serving vendor, Google. The link is http://www.google.com/settings/ads/onweb/.Third-Party and Online Behavioral Advertising Opt-out – Please visit this link to opt-out of cookies from more than 50 major third-party behavioral advertising providers. The link is http://www.aboutads.info/choices/.We will never (and will not allow any third party to) use the statistical analytics tool to track or to collect any Personally Identifiable Information (PII) of visitors to our site. Google will not associate your IP address with any other data held by Google. Neither we nor Google will link, or seek to link, an IP address with the identity of a computer user. We will not associate any data gathered from this site with any PII from any source unless you explicitly submit that information via a fill-in form on our website.
we want to hear about your case
connect with us facebook twitter linkedin youtube yelp rss
